ultimatenichefinder.com 2016-09-01

# Privacy Policy - Ultimate Niche Finder

Ultimate Niche Finder LLC is committed to safeguard your privacy on-line. The following statement sets our privacy policy. For the purpose of this Privacy Statement “UNF” shall mean UltimateNicheFinder.com. This policy may change from time to time so please re-read this policy periodically.

**Information we gather**

Our site collects information in several ways. When you sign up with our UNF services, you are required to complete a registration form. UNF requests your “Contact Information” like your name, email address, financial information (such as payment details and credit card details) and your address and phone number. Credit card information is not stored on our servers. Credit card information is stored by Stripe.com.

**How we use the information we gather**

The Contact Information from the registration form is used to register users in our database, and is also used to get in touch with them when necessary. UNF does not collect or store any financial information. Secure online payments are provided by Stripe.com, Inc.

**The people that are given access to this information**

You should note that the Contact Information you have provided will not be made publicly available, nor sold to third parties.

UNF may disclose Contact Information in special cases where UNF has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms and conditions of use or may be causing injury or interference with our rights, property, our customers or anyone who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose Contact Information when we believe, in good faith, that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes necessary to maintain services and improve our products and services.

**The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information**

Our site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please note, however, that no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. As a result, while we attempt to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission we attempt to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems.

**Our use of cookies**

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalize your experience of our website.
